[
  {
    "question": "What is the output of the following code? \n console.log(2 + '2');",
    "options": ["22", "4", "NaN", "undefined"],
    "answer": "22",
    "category": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "category": "JavaScript",
    "question": "What is the output of the following code: console.log(typeof [])?",
    "options": ["'array'", "'object'", "'null'", "'undefined'"],
    "answer": "'object'"
  },
  {
    "category": "JavaScript",
    "question": "What keyword is used to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
    "options": ["let", "var", "const", "all of the above"],
    "answer": "let"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is used to add an element to the end of an array in JavaScript?",
    "options": ["unshift()", "push()", "splice()", "concat()"],
    "answer": "push()",
    "category": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result of the following expression? \n 5 == '5'",
    "options": ["true", "false", "undefined", "null"],
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correct way to write a JavaScript function?",
    "options": [
      "function = myFunction()",
      "myFunction = function()",
      "function myFunction()",
      "function:myFunction()"
    ],
    "answer": "function myFunction()",
    "category": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a loop statement in JavaScript?",
    "options": ["for", "if", "switch", "try"],
    "answer": "for",
    "category": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "category": "JavaScript",
    "question": "Which of the following is a valid way to check if an object has a certain property?",
    "options": [
      "obj.hasOwnProperty('prop')",
      "obj.contains('prop')",
      "obj.property('prop')",
      "obj.key('prop')"
    ],
    "answer": "obj.hasOwnProperty('prop')"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result of the following expression? \n typeof(null)",
    "options": ["undefined", "null", "object", "none of the above"],
    "answer": "object",
    "category": "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    "category": "JavaScript",
    "question": "Which keyword is used to declare a constant variable in JavaScript?",
    "options": ["let", "var", "const", "const var"],
    "answer": "const"
  },
  {
    "category": "JavaScript",
    "question": "What is the result of the following code: '5' * 2;",
    "options": ["10", "'52'", "7", "NaN"],
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "category": "JavaScript",
    "question": "What is the difference between let and const in JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "let variables can be reassigned, while const variables cannot",
      "const variables can be reassigned, while let variables cannot",
      "let variables have function scope, while const variables have block scope",
      "const variables have function scope, while let variables have block scope"
    ],
    "answer": "let variables can be reassigned, while const variables cannot"
  },
  {
    "category": "JavaScript",
    "question": "What is the output of the following code: console.log('foo'.split('').reverse().join(''));",
    "options": ["'foo'", "'ofo'", "'f'", "'oof'"],
    "answer": "'oof'"
  }
]
